<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!DOCTYPE categories
[
<!ELEMENT categories (sneakers, beverages)>
<!ELEMENT sneakers (categoriesItem*)>
<!ELEMENT others (sports, slipers)>
<!ELEMENT sports (categoriesItem*)>
<!ELEMENT slipers (categoriesItem*)>
<!ELEMENT menuItem (name?, size?, price, description?)>
<!ELEMENT name (#PCDATA)>
<!ELEMENT size (#PCDATA)>
<!ELEMENT price (#PCDATA)>
<!ELEMENT description (#PCDATA)>
<!ELEMENT imageURL (#PCDATA)>
]>

<categories>
    <sneakers>
     <categoriesItem>
            <name>
                NIKE AIR JORDAN ZY009
            </name>
            <price>
                520.00
            </price>
            <description>
                Step into sleek style and unbeatable performance with the NIKE AIR JORDAN ZY009, featuring a breathable mesh upper, durable rubber outsole, and iconic swoosh logo for the ultimate blend of comfort and athletic elegance.
            </description>
            <imageURL>1.jpg</imageURL>
        </categoriesItem>
        <categoriesItem>
            <name>
                PUMA V12 LEATHER
            </name>
            <price>
                469.00
            </price>
            <description>
               Elevate your stride with the PUMA V12 LEATHER in OLIVE GREEN, crafted with premium leather, sleek design, and PUMA's signature comfort technology for a luxurious fusion of style and performance.
            </description>
            <imageURL>2.jpg</imageURL>
        </categoriesItem>
        <categoriesItem>
            <name>
                ADIDAS BLACK MOON BATMAN 
            </name>
            <price>
                259.00
            </price>
            <description>
               Sleek, stylish, and comfortable, these shoes elevate your look with a bold it's design and premium materials for confident strides in every step.
            </description>
            <imageURL>3.jpg</imageURL>
        </categoriesItem>
        <categoriesItem>
            <name>
                NEW BALANCE SMART CASUAL Y1
            </name>
            <price>
                219.00
            </price>
            <description>
               Introducing New Balance CNY Rare shoes, a limited-edition celebration of style and heritage, perfect for discerning collectors seeking standout additions to their inventory.
            </description>
            <imageURL>4.jpg</imageURL>
        </categoriesItem>
        <categoriesItem>
            <name>
                NEW BALANCE BEST MOON WALKING
            </name>
            <price>
                750.00
            </price>
            <description>
                Explore the New Balance Best Moon Walking shoes, meticulously crafted for unparalleled comfort and style, ideal for moonlit strolls and urban adventures alike.
            </description>
            <imageURL>5.jpg</imageURL>
        </categoriesItem>
        <categoriesItem>
            <name>
                NIKE AIRMAX D14
            </name>
            <price>
                569.00
            </price>
            <description>
                Discover the Nike AirMax D14, a fusion of style and performance engineered to elevate your stride with unparalleled comfort and iconic Nike design.
            </description>
            <imageURL>6.jpg</imageURL>
        </categoriesItem>
        <categoriesItem>
            <name>
                PUMA XSHREDDED 2
            </name>
            <price>
                699.00
            </price>
            <description>
                Unveil the Puma XShredded 2, a pinnacle of style and performance, designed to enhance your workout with cutting-edge technology and Puma's signature flair.
            </description>
            <imageURL>7.jpg</imageURL>
        </categoriesItem>
        <categoriesItem>
            <name>
                VANS X PADIN
            </name>
            <price>
                469.99
            </price>
            <description>
               Introducing the Vans X Padin Musa Malaysia collaboration, a unique blend of Malaysian heritage and Vans' iconic style, bringing a touch of local culture to your footwear collection.
            </description>
            <imageURL>8.jpg</imageURL>
        </categoriesItem>
    </sneakers>
    <others>
        <sports>
            <categoriesItem>
                <name>
                    PUMA XBOLT SPIKES    
                </name>
                <price>
                    539.99
                </price>
                <description>
                    Experience the Puma XBOLT Spikes: crafted for speed, precision, and unmatched performance on the track.
                </description>
                <imageURL>9.jpg</imageURL>
            </categoriesItem>
            <categoriesItem>
                <name>
                    NIKE AIRMAX RUNNING SHOES X12   
                </name>
                <price>
                    559.00
                </price>
                <description>
                    Unleash your potential with Nike AirMax Running Shoes X12, engineered for exceptional performance with a blend of comfort, style, and innovation.
                </description>
                <imageURL>10.jpg</imageURL>
            </categoriesItem>
            <categoriesItem>
                <name>
                    NEW BALANCE SPARKING P1   
                </name>
                <price>
                    524.00
                </price>
                <description>
                    The 1080 delivers top-of-the-line performance to every kind of runner, whether you’re training for world-class competition, or catching a rush hour train. 
                </description>
                <imageURL>11.jpg</imageURL>
            </categoriesItem>
        </sports>
        <slipers>
            <categoriesItem>
                <name>
                    SKETCHERS NEW FLIP FLOP WOMEN WEARS    
                </name>
                <price>
                    249.00
                </price>
                <description>
                    TStep into comfort and style with Skechers' latest Flip Flop for women, designed to elevate your summer wardrobe with effortless chic and unparalleled comfort. 
                </description>                
                <imageURL>12.jpg</imageURL>
            </categoriesItem>
            <categoriesItem>
                <name>
                    BONIA STYLISH ELLISH    
                </name>
                <price>
                    230.00
                </price>
                <description>
                Elevate your comfort and style with Bonia Stylish Ellish slippers, crafted with luxurious materials and sleek design to add a touch of sophistication to your everyday loungewear.
                </description> 
                <imageURL>13.jpg</imageURL>
            </categoriesItem>
            <categoriesItem>
                <name>
                    CROCS X Lisa Frank Classic Clogs    
                </name>
                <price>
                    479.34
                </price>
                <description>
               Experience the playful charm of Crocs X Lisa Frank Classic Clogs in kids' sizes, where iconic design meets comfort, bringing joy and color to every step.
                </description> 
                <imageURL>14.jpg</imageURL>
            </categoriesItem>
        </slipers>
    </others>
</categories>
